<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.htmlhifive.tools.tomcat"
      label="hifive Tomcat Plugin"
      version="3.3.0.vqualifier"
      plugin="com.sysdeo.eclipse.tomcat">

   <description>
      hifive tomcat plugin
   </description>

   <copyright>
      -TomcatPlugin
    (c) Copyright Sysdeo SA 2001, 2002.
    All Rights Reserved.
  -Tomcat Feature
    Copyright (C) 2012-2016 NS Solutions Corporation.
   </copyright>

   <license url="">
      -TomcatPlugin
      License
    Sysdeo makes available all content in this plug-in. The plug-in is provided to you under the terms and conditions of the MIT License. For purposes of the MIT License,
    &quot;Software&quot; will mean the plug-in.
      The MIT License
      Copyright (c) 2002 Sysdeo
      Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the
      &quot;Software&quot;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute,
      sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following
      conditions:
      The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
      THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO
      THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL
      THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF
      CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER
      DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.

  -TomcatFeature
    Copyright (C) 2012-2016 NS Solutions Corporation.
    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &quot;License&quot;);
    you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
    You may obtain a copy of the License at
    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,
    WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
    See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
    limitations under the License
   </license>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.swt"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.launching"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.debug"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.debug.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="com.sysdeo.eclipse.tomcat"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

</feature>
